question_data = [
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "In &quot;The Sims&quot; series, the most members in a household you can have is 8.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "This is the correct spelling of &quot;Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "In the comic book &quot;Archie&quot;, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science & Nature",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "It was once believed that injecting shark cartilage into people would prevent them from contracting cancer.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Mythology",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Rannamaari was a sea demon that haunted the people of the Maldives and had to be appeased monthly with the sacrifice of a virgin girl.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "The names of Roxas&#039;s Keyblades in Kingdom Hearts are &quot;Oathkeeper&quot; and &quot;Oblivion&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "The board game Go has more possible legal positions than the number of atoms in the visible universe.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science & Nature",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "The value of one Calorie is different than the value of one calorie.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "The weapon Clint Eastwood uses in &quot;Dirty Harry&quot; was a .44 Automag.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "In the &quot;Kagerou Daze&quot; series, Shintaro Kisaragi is prominently shown with the color red.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
]